Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority: Metro History Project Collection, 1930-1984 MS2034
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority: Metro History Project Collection
1930-1984
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Metro 2001, Inc
MS2034
8.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, clippings, transcripts of speeches and Congressional hearings, bound volumes, cassette tapes, and maps that document the history of the development of rapid transit facilities for the Washington metropolitan area. The records date from 1930 to 1984.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Metro History Project was a project of Metro 2001, Inc., an organization founded in 1979 to produce a book-length history of the Metro for the Washington Metropolitan Transit Authority. Using documents obtained from local archives and private collections, Metro 2001, Inc. produced several short works entitled "Metro History Monographs." Although many of these documents were cataloged and entered into a database to be indexed, the book was never completed and the project was abandoned. The materials were donated to The George Washington University in 1985. Related material can be found in the papers of C. Darwin Stolzenbach.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, clippings, transcripts of speeches and Congressional hearings, bound volumes, cassette tapes, and maps that document the history of the development of rapid transit facilities for the Washington metropolitan area. The records date from 1930 to 1984.
Because the numbering system assigned to the items does not reflect chronological or alphabetical order, the Project's indexes should be consulted first. These include a document index, a photograph index, an index of proposed chapters to never-completed book, and a Global Index. The oral history transcripts are often incomplete or paraphrased, so they should only be used for overview purposes. The tapes contain the complete original interviews.
Collection Organization
Organized into five series: Historical documents, Photograph file lists, Publications, Oral histories, and Oversized documents.
Washington (D.C.); United States. Congress; Transportation maps; Speeches; Washington (D.C.) -- History; Subways; Transportation; Washington Metropolitan Area; Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority
- Historical documents, 1930-1984; MS2034 Series 1; 6.25 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series, representing the largest portion of the collection, contains documents including Congressional hearings, correspondence, and clippings dating from 1930 to 1984. It also contains an index of the documents.
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1-60, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 61-110, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 111-142, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 143-170, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 171-200, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 201-240, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 241-290, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 291-360, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 361-430, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 431-480, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 481-550, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 551-619, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 620-690, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 691-799, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 800-849, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 850-1010, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1011-1130, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1131-1215, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1216-1450, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1451-1540, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1541-1605, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1606-1749, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1750-1810, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Abstract Index: Metro History Abstracts, File Numbers 1811-1899, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1-la, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts Ib-lc, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts Id, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts le, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 2-30, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 61-80, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 81-90, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 91-98, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 31-60, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 99-101, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 102-104, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 105a-107b, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 107-112, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 113-122, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 124a-130h, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 131-143, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 144a-n, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 145a-158, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 159a-160b, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 162-1 71f, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 172-177, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 178a-185c, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 186a-b, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 187a-e, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 187f-h, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 187i-190b, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 191a- 195, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 197a-200, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 201-220, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 221-229g, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 234-239, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 246-280, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 281-329, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 332-360, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 362-405, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 406-440, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 441, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 444-461, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 463-469, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 474-483, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 495-520, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 521-549, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 549a-550, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 551-587, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 588, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 589-594a, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 595-620, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 621-630, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 631-640, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 641-670, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 671-683, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 692-708, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 709-720, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 721-723, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 724-730, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 731-770, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 771-780, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 781-790, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 791-800, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 801-820, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 821-830, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 831-840, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 841-850, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 851-870, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 891-907, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 908-930, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 931-1005b, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1007a-1017, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1018a-b, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1019a-d, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1020a-1025, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1026, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1027, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1028, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1029, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1030, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1100-1115, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1116-1126, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1127-1130, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1131-1144b, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1145-1170, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1171-1180, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1181-1196, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1197-1200, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1201-1229, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1231-1407, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1408-1411, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1413-1430, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1441-1450, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1452-1460, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1461-1470, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1471-1480, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1481-1490, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1501-1530, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1531-1543, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1544, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1545-1558, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1561-1580, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1581-1588, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1589, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1590-1600, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1601-1606b, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1607-1616, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1700a-1720, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1721-1736, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1737-1750, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1751-1760, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1762-1780, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1781-1788, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1789-1791, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1792, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1797-1799, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1800, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1801-1809, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 181 la- 1824, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1825-1844, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1845-1860, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1881-1890, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts 1891-2010, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Metro History Abstracts unnumbered, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Photograph file lists, undated; MS2034 Series 2; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series contains indexes to 491 photogaphs housed at the WMATA. The lists index the images by year, line number, name, place, and subject.
  - Chronological Index, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Line Index, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Name Index, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Place Index, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Subject Index, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Photo Abstracts records 1-256, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Photo Abstracts records 257-491, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Publications, undated; MS2034 Series 3; 0.75 Linear feet
  This series contains indexes for each proposed chapter of the Metro History Project book, broken down by type of index. Copies of the monographs resulting from the Metro History Project are also included.
  - Chapter 1, Authors, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 1, Subchapters, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 1, Subjects, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 1, Summary, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 2, Authors, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 2, Subchapters, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 2, Subjects, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 2, Summary, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 4, Authors, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 4, Subchapters, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 4, Subjects, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 4, Summary, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 5, Authors, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 5, Subchapters, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 5, Subjects, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 5, Summary, pages 1-55, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 5, Summary, Pages 56-115, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 6, Authors, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 6, Subchapters, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 6, Subjects, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 6, Summary, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 7, Authors, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 7, Subchapters, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 7, Subjects, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 7, Summary, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 8, Authors, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 8, Subchapters, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 8, Subjects, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 8, Summary, pages 1-45, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 8, Summary, pages 46-91, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 9, Authors, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 9, Subchapters, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 9, Subjects, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 9, Summary, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 10, Authors, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 10, Subchapters, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 10, Subjects, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 10, Summary, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Chapter 11, Authors, Subjects, and Summary, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Chapter 12, Summary, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Metro History Monograph, "The Authorization of Metro", undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Metro History Monograph, "The History of the Mass Transportation Survey", undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Metro History Monograph,, "Roles of Local Officials in the Creation of Metro", undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Oral histories, 1975-1983; MS2034 Series 4; 1 Linear feet
  This series contains transcripts, summarys of interviews, and cassette tapes of oral histories. Transcripts are often incomplete or paraphrased and vary in format. The date from 1975 to 1983.
  - Summary: Interview with Cleatus Barnett, 1981 November (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Harland Bartholomew, 1979 March (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Frederick J. Clarke, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Summary: Interview with Walter Fauntroy, 1982 January (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Joseph Fischer, 1981 November (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Francis Francois, 1981 December (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Summary: Interview with James Gleason, 1982 January (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Summary: Interview with Herbert Harris, 1981 October (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts: Interview with George Hartzog, 1981 June (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Keneth Hoover, 1979 May (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Charles Horsky, 1981 November (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Robert Keith, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Summary: Interview with Jerry Moore, 1982 March (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Summary: Interview with John Nevis, 1981 November; MS2034 Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts: Interview with McKim Norton, 1979 May (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Summary: Interview with Carlton Sickles, 1981 October (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Summary: Interview with Sterling Tucker, 1981 November (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Francis Turner, 1982 February (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Summary: Interview with Paul Watt, 1981 October (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Herbert Wells, 1979 July (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Transcripts: Interview with Basil Whitener, 1982 November (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Tapes: Samuel Abbott; James Gleason, 1982 January 07-1983 May 12 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Tapes: Cleatus Barnett; Walter Fauntroy, 1981 November 05-1982 January 18 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Tapes: Harland Bartholomew, 1979 March 27 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Tapes: Alan Boyd; George Hertzog, 1981 June 23-1982 August 11 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Tapes: Charles Conrad, 1981 October 14 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Tapes: William Finley, 1982 May 20 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Tapes: Joseph Fischer; Herbert Harris, 1981 November 18-October 21 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Tapes: Jackson Graham, part 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Tapes: Jackson Graham, part 2; Paul Watt, part 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tapes: Jackson Graham, part 3, 1981 October 05 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Tapes: Jackson Graham, part 4, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Tapes: Frederick Gutheim, part 1, 1982 April 09 - 19 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Tapes: Frederick Gutheim, part 2, 1982 April 19 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Tapes: Philip Hammer, 1982 December 22 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Tapes: Keneth Hoover, 1979 May 04 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Tapes: Charles Horsky; Paul Watt, part 2, 1981 December 02-October 02 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Tapes: Robert Keith; Frederick Clarke, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Tapes: John Nevius; Sterling Tucker, 1981 November 10-20 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Tapes: McKim Norton, part 1, 1979 May 04 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Tapes: McKim Norton, part 2, 1979 May 04 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Tapes: Wilfred Owen, 1982 February 09 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Tapes: John Rannells, 1981 October 16 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Tapes: Cody Pfanstiehl, 1983 April 06 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Tapes: Warren Quenstedt, 1982 November 06 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Tapes: Elizabeth Rowe; Francis Francois, 1981 October 21-December 29 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Tapes: Carlton Sickles; Leo Urbanski, 1981 October 26 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Tapes: Frank Turner, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Tapes: Harry Weese and Lyle Fitch, 1981 September 02-1982 June 03 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Tapes: Herbert Wells, 1975 July 23 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Tapes: Max Wehrly, 1982 June 09 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Tapes: Hugh Wynn, 1981 June 02 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Tapes: Basil Whitener [tape 1], 1982 November 13 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Tapes: Basil Whitener (tape 2) and Edwin Seeger, 1982 November 11-November 18 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Oversized documents, 1983; MS2034 Series 5; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series contains a Global Index by author, title, name, organization, and subject. It is the most comprehensive set of indexes available for referencing the historical documents in Series 1.
  - Global Index: Authors, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Global Index: Document Titles, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Global Index: Document Titles, chronological, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Global Index: Key names, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Global Index: Organizations, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Global Index: Subjects, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - ATP Speed Commands, Control line drawings, 1973 March 19-July 12 (Map-folder 18)